Contact

niluk93@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nilesh-krishnan-58501667 (LinkedIn) niluk93.github.io/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Game Development Programming Unreal Engine 4

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Tamil (Native or Bilingual)

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Nilesh Krishnan

Programmer at A44

New Zealand

Summary

I'm a game developer who has been working in the industry for a bit over 5 years. I am quite experienced with C++ and C#, along with game engines such as Unreal Engine, Unity and Godot. I am also quite comfortable with working on custom game engines and using a wide array of libraries. I have also worked on titles ranging across multiple platforms, including PC, Console and Mobile.

Experience

A44

Programmer September 2019 - Present

Wellington & Wairarapa, New Zealand

Sumo Video Games
Game Programmer
July 2016 - August 2019 (3 years 2 months)
Pune Area, India

Purple Talk Software Engineer January 2014 - February 2016 (2 years 2 months) Hyderabad Area, India

BlueGiant Interactive
Game Tester
August 2012 - October 2012 (3 months)
Hyderabad, India

Education

Backstage Pass - School of Gaming

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science and Game Development · (2011 - 2015)

P.M.M. Inner Wheel School · (1997 - 2009)